A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Corporation, Board of Directors/Board of Scientific Directors, Minutes FA856
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Minutes of meetings, 1901 May 1-1953 June 23; 1 package (10 volumes) (Package 2)
  - Space for Thomas M. Rivers command headquarters for U.S. Naval Research Unit No. 2, 1944 June 5
  - Memorial minute, Alexis Carrel, 1873-1944, 1945 April 21
  - Memorial minute, Max Bergmann, 1886-1944, 1945 April 21
  - Memorial minute, Walter Bradford Cannon, 1871-1945, 1946 January 18
  - Transcript of memorial service for Simon Flexner filed with records of Board, 1946 June 1
  - Memorial minute, Charles Lee Hoagland, 1907-1946, 1947 January 18
  - Summary of discussion of Director's memorandum suggesting unification of Princeton and New York departments, 1947 April 19
  - Resolution from Board of Trustees recommending unification of Princeton and New York departments, 1947 June 7
  - Memorial minute, Leonor Michaelis, 1875-1949, 1950 January 21
  - Closing of Princeton plant, 1950 October 27
  - Memorial minute, James Bumgardner Murphy, 1884-1950, 1951 January 20
  - Resolution on retirement: Warfield T. Longcope, 1952 January 23
  - Vote that existing Rules of Board of Scientific Directors be repealed, and that present By-laws of Corporation be repealed and the new By-laws of the Corporation, as circulated in advance be adopted, 1953 June 23